const questions = [
  {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to manage a housing estate?",
    options: [
      "1. A high school dropout with no experience in property management",
      "2. A self-taught handyman who has never managed property before",
      "3. A licensed and experienced property manager with positive references",
    ],
    answer:
      "3. A licensed and experienced property manager with positive references",
  },
  {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to repair your car's engine?",
    options: [
      "1. A librarian who has never worked on a car before",
      "2. A friend who tinkers with cars as a hobby",
      "3. A professional auto mechanic with good reviews",
      "4. A preschool teacher with no relevant experience",
    ],
    answer: "3. A professional auto mechanic with good reviews",
  },
  {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to plan your wedding?",
    options: [
      "1. A celebrity chef who has never planned an event before",
      "2. A family member who is not well-organized",
      "3. A professional wedding planner with experience and good reviews",
      "4. A teenager with no event planning experience",
    ],
    answer:
      "3. A professional wedding planner with experience and good reviews",
  },
  {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to handle your investments?",
    options: [
      "1. A psychic who claims to have insider trading knowledge",
      "2. A close friend with no experience in finance",
      "3. A licensed and reputable financial advisor with good references",
      "4. A taxi driver with no knowledge of the stock market",
    ],
    answer:
      "3. A licensed and reputable financial advisor with good references",
  },
  {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to teach you how to swim?",
    options: [
      "1.  A person who is afraid of the water",
      "2. A professional swimming coach with certifications and experience",
      "3.  A person who only knows how to doggy paddle",
      "4. A musician with no knowledge of swimming",
    ],
    answer:
      "2. A professional swimming coach with certifications and experience",
  },
  {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to provide medical advice?",
    options: [
      "1. A YouTuber with no medical background",
      "2. A medical doctor with a good reputation and credentials",
      "3. A personal trainer with no medical education",
      "4. A politician who claims to have secret medical knowledge",
    ],
    answer: "2. A medical doctor with a good reputation and credentials",
  },
  {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to give you a haircut?",
    options: [
      "1. A person with no experience in hair styling",
      "2. A professional hairstylist with good reviews",
      "3. A painter with no knowledge of hair care",
      "4.  A student who is practicing hair styling for the first time",
    ],
    answer: "2. A professional hairstylist with good reviews",
  },
  {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to design your website?",
    options: [
      "1. A friend who knows how to use Microsoft Word",
      "2. A professional web designer with experience and a portfolio",
      "3. A person who has never used a computer before",
      "4. A comedian with no knowledge of web design",
    ],
    answer: "2. A professional web designer with experience and a portfolio",
  },
  {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to babysit your child?",
    options: [
      "1. A person who has a criminal record for child abuse",
      "2. A licensed and experienced childcare provider with good references",
      "3. A teenager who has never cared for a child before",
      "4. A person who is not good with children",
    ],
    answer:
      "2. A licensed and experienced childcare provider with good references",
  },
  {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to handle your legal matters?",
    options: [
      "1. A person who claims to be a lawyer but has no law degree",
      "2. A licensed and reputable attorney with a good track record",
      "3. A politician who makes promises to solve legal issues",
      "4. A chef with no knowledge",
    ],
    answer: "2. A licensed and reputable attorney with a good track record",
  },
  /*   {
    questionText: "Who would you trust to handle your legal matters?",
    options: ["1. break", "2. stop", "3. halt", "4. exit"],
    answer: "1. break",
  }, */
]

export default questions
